A Finding Aid to the Architectural League of New York Records, 1880s-1974, bulk 1927-1968, in the Archives of American Art AAA.archleag
Archives of American Art
- Functions and Events, 1909, 1931-1973; Series 6; 9.35 Linear feet Boxes 84-9, OV 120
  - Functions and Events Sponsored by Others, 1941-1966; 6.2
    - 1951 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 90)
      - American Society of Landscape Architects, Miscellaneous Dinners, 1951-1956 (Box 90, Folder 65)
      - The Municipal Art Society Luncheons, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 66)
      - Phi Kappa Psi Dinners, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 67)
      - National Sculpture Society Dinners, Dining Room (Jan. 12 - Feb. 13, 1951), 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 68)
      - Sheila Burlingame Cocktail Party, Pine Room (Jan. 15, 1951, 4pm) (Box 90, Folder 69)
      - Lithographers National Association Luncheon, Pine Room (Jan. 18, 1951), 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 70)
      - S.A.D.G. Cocktails and Dinner, Pine Room, Gallery "A" (Jan. 25, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 71)
      - American Institute of Graphic Arts Cocktail Party, Gallery "A" (Jan. 29, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 72)
      - M.I.T. Dinner and Party, Gallery "A," Dining Room (Feb. 1, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 73)
      - National Lithographers Association Cocktail Party (Feb. 21, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 74)
      - New York Chapter, American Society of Landscape Architects Dinner (Feb. 21, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 75)
      - Art Directors Luncheons, Pine Room, 7 Fridays (Mar. 26 - Apr. 27, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 76)
      - Producers' Council Luncheon (Tue., Mar. 27, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 77)
      - M.I.T. Dance (Apr. 6, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 78)
      - National Sculpture Society Dinner (Apr. 10, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 79)
      - Beaux Arts Institute of Design Dinner (Apr. 19, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 80)
      - A.I.A. Pre-Convention Luncheon (Apr. 24, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 81)
      - M. Proctor, Freeman and Mueser Dinner (May 4, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 82)
      - Fine Arts Federation Luncheons (May 7, Nov. 11, Nov. 15, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 83)
      - National Sculpture Society Dinner (May 8, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 84)
      - Producers' Council Luncheons (May 8, June 28, Dec. 4, 1951), 1951-1952 (Box 90, Folder 85)
      - Art Directors Dinner (May 14, 1951), 1951-1952 (Box 90, Folder 86)
      - Architectural Photographs Cocktail Party (May 22, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 87)
      - Structural Engineers Society of New York Luncheons (May 22, Oct. 30, 1951), 1951-1952 (Box 90, Folder 88)
      - Committee Residence Lighting Forum and Tea (June 5, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 89)
      - American Academy in Rome Dinner, Pine Room (June 6, 1951), circa 1951 (Box 90, Folder 90)
      - Architects' Emergency Committee Luncheons (June 11, Nov. 6, Dec. 6, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 91)
      - My Kitchen Contest Luncheon (Aug. 23, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 92)
      - Fazakas Cocktail Party (Sept. 17 and 18, 195[1?]), circa 1951 (Box 90, Folder 93)
      - National Sculpture Society Dinner (Oct. 9, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 94)
      - Quiet Birdmen Dinner (Oct. 15, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 95)
      - Miracle Adhesive Corporation Cocktail Party (Oct. 23, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 96)
      - B.A.I.D. School Luncheon (Oct. 24, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 97)
      - Pictorial Photographers Punch Party (Nov. 6, [1951?]), circa 1951 (Box 90, Folder 98)
      - Lambda Alpha Fraternity Dinner and Meeting (Nov. 16, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 99)
      - Beaux Arts Institute of Design Annual Dinner (Nov. 29, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 100)
      - Masta Display Cocktail Party (Dec. 3, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 101)
      - National Sculpture Society Dinner (Dec. 11, 1951?), circa 1951 (Box 90, Folder 102)
      - Appalachian Mountain Club Dinner (Dec. 13, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 103)
      - Albert W. Butt, Jr. Cocktail Party at His Office (Dec. 21, 1951) (Box 90, Folder 104)
    - 1952 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 90)
      - American Institute of Architects Dinners, 1952 (Box 90, Folder 105)
      - Bard-St. Stephen's Alumni Association Cocktail Party, 1952 (Box 90, Folder 106)
      - Fine Arts Federation Luncheon, 1952-1953 (Box 90, Folder 107)
      - General Precision Laboratory, 1952-1954 (Box 90, Folder 108)
      - The Municipal Art Society, 1952-1953 (Box 90, Folder 109)
      - M.I.T. Club Luncheon (Jan. 9?, 1952), 1951 (Box 90, Folder 110)
      - Chessmen Luncheon (Jan. 10, 1952), 1951-1952 (Box 90, Folder 111)
      - The City College Evening Meeting and Refreshments (Jan. 18, 1952), 1951 (Box 90, Folder 112)
      - Snipe Class International Racing Association Dinner (Jan. 18, 1952), 1951 (Box 90, Folder 113)
      - Industrial Design Institute Cocktail Party and Meeting (Jan. 25, 1952) (Box 90, Folder 114)
      - Stockwell (Hamill) Cocktail Parties (Feb. 1952) (Box 90, Folder 115)
      - Eastern Division of the Model Yacht Racing Association of America Meeting (Feb. 16, 1952, 1:30pm) (Box 90, Folder 116)
      - New York Society of Landscape Architects Dinner (Feb. 19, Mar. 18, 1952) (Box 90, Folder 117)
      - Quiet Birdmen Dinner and Birthday Party (Feb. 25, 1952) (Box 90, Folder 118)
      - Rhode Island Club of New York Dinner (Apr. 24, 1952) (Box 90, Folder 119)
      - Alpha Rho Chi Dinner and Meeting (June 25, 1952) (Box 90, Folder 120)
    - 1953 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 90)
      - American Institute of Architects Dinners, 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 121)
      - American Institute of Architects Luncheons, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 122)
      - American Society of Landscape Architects Dinner, circa 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 123)
      - Art Directors Annual Meeting and Dinner, circa 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 124)
      - Art Directors Luncheons, 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 125)
      - Beaux-Arts Annual Dinners, 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 126)
      - Carnegie Alumni Clan Luncheons, 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 127)
      - Cherry Lawn School, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 128)
      - Columbia University Dinner, 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 129)
      - Columbia University Luncheon, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 130)
      - Construction Specification Institute Dinner, 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 131)
      - Fine Arts Federation Luncheons, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 132)
      - Industrial Designers Institute Dinners, 1953-1956 (Box 90, Folder 133)
      - M.I.T. Class of 1911, 1953-1955 (Box 90, Folder 134)
      - New York Society of Medical Artists Cocktail Party, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 135)
      - Phi Kappa Psi Luncheons, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 136)
      - Producers' Council Luncheons, 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 137)
      - Quiet Birdmen, 1953-1956 (Box 90, Folder 138)
      - Structural Engineers Society of New York Luncheon, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 139)
      - Structural Engineers Society of New York Luncheon, Pine Room (Jan. 16, 1953) (Box 90, Folder 140)
    - 1953 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Fisker Evening (Mar. 11, 1953) (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Franklin X. McCormick Dinner (Apr. 28, 1953) (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - American Academy in Rome Dinner (May 1953) (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Pratt Institute Cocktail Party, Khosrov Ajootian (May 5, 1953) (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Art Directors President's Party, Dinner (June 9, 1953) (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - New York State Association of Architects (Sept. 12, 1953) (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Perry Coke Smith Meeting (Oct. 26, 1953) (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Forest Hills Lodge #946 F. and A.M. Dance (Dec. 5, 1953) (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - 1954 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Amateur Ski Club, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Amateur Ski Club Luncheon, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - American Institute of Architects Dinners, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - American Institute of Architects Luncheons, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - American Institute of Decorators Dinner, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Architects' Council Luncheons, 1954-1956 (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - Columbia University Class of 1928 Luncheon, George D. Brown, Jr., 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 15)
      - Construction Specifications Institute Dinners, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 16)
      - Eastern "T.F." Club Luncheon Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 17)
      - Fine Arts Federation Luncheons, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 18)
      - The Haddon Craftsmen, Inc., 1954 (Box 91, Folder 19)
      - H. Lieblich and Co. Meetings, Asher B. Etkes, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 20)
      - M.I.T. Luncheons, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 21)
      - The Municipal Arts Society Luncheon, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 22)
      - National Sculpture Society Dinners and Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 23)
      - New York Society of Architects Meetings, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 24)
      - Producers' Council Luncheons, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 25)
      - Rho Psi Fraternity Dinner, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 26)
      - Terra Cotta Corporation Luncheon, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 27)
      - Theta Delta Chi Luncheon Meetings, 1954-1956 (Box 91, Folder 28)
      - M.I.T. Lunch, Pine Room (Jan. 12, 1954), 1953 (Box 91, Folder 29)
      - Illuminating Engineering Society, School Lighting Clinic (Jan. 28, 1954) (Box 91, Folder 30)
      - McCall's Judgment and Luncheon (Feb. 1, 2, 1954) (Box 91, Folder 31)
      - Pratt Institute Department of Architecture Cocktail Party (July 1, 1954) (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - 1955 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - B.A.I.D. Annual Dinner, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 33)
      - Columbia University Luncheon, 1955-1956 (Box 91, Folder 34)
      - Home Fashion League Luncheons, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 35)
      - Lambda Alpha Fraternity Luncheons, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 36)
      - Men's Garden Club of New York City, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 37)
      - Metropolitan Stereo Club, 1955-1957 (Box 91, Folder 38)
      - New York Alumni Association Phi Kappa Psi, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 39)
      - New York Business Paper Editors Association Luncheons, First Monday of the Month, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 40)
      - The New York Numismatic Club Dinner, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 41)
      - Theta Delta Chi Dinner, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 42)
    - 1956 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - American Institute of Architects Events, 1956-1958 (Box 91, Folder 43)
      - Architectural Photographers Association Meetings, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 44)
      - Art Directors Club of New York Luncheons, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 45)
      - Art Directors Las Vegas Party, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 46)
      - Bard-St. Stephen's Alumni Association Cocktail Party, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 47)
      - Bard-St. Stephen's Alumni Meeting and Cocktail Party, Pine Room, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 48)
      - Carnegie Institute of Technology Luncheon Meetings, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 49)
      - Construction Specification Institute, Inc. Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 50)
      - Eastern Division of the Model Yacht Racing Association of America, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 51)
      - The Edward Macdowell Association Meeting, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 52)
      - Holophane Company Luncheon Meetings, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 53)
      - Industrial Decorative Designers, Meetings and Mailing Service Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 54)
      - Lambda Alpha Fraternity Luncheon, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 55)
      - The Municipal Art Society Luncheon Meetings, 1956-1958 (Box 91, Folder 56)
      - National Institute for Architectural Education (B.A.I.D.) Dinners, 1956-1959 (Box 91, Folder 57)
      - National Sculpture Society Dinners, 1956-1958 (Box 91, Folder 58)
      - New York Alumni Association Luncheons, Mr. Ernest H. Garbe, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 59)
      - New York Chapter of the A.I.A. Dinners, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 60)
      - New York State Association of Architects Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 61)
      - Quiet Birdmen, Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 62)
      - Quiet Birdmen's Dinners, (Special) Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 91, Folder 63)
      - Producers' Council Luncheons, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 64)
      - Shaker Village, Mr. Jerome Count, Director, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 65)
      - Westinghouse Electric Company Meeting and Buffet Supper, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 66)
      - Illuminating Engineering Society Dinner (May 24, 1956) (Box 91, Folder 67)
    - 1957 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 68)
      - Big Brothers Movement Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 91, Folder 69)
      - Carnegie Tech H. Leiblich Dinner, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 70)
      - Cherry Lawn School Tea, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 71)
      - Director's Art Institute, David Bradshaw Meeting, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 72)
      - The Edward MacDowell Association Meeting, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 73)
      - New York Chapter, American Institute of Decorators, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 74)
      - Package Designers Council Dinner, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 75)
      - Phi Kappa Psi Fraternity Luncheon, Ernest H. Garbe, 1957-1958 (Box 91, Folder 76)
      - Veteran Motor Car Club of America Buffet Dinner, Ernest W. Congdon, Jr., 1957-1958 (Box 91, Folder 77)
      - American Society of Landscape Architects Dinner (Oct. 24, 1957) (Box 91, Folder 78)
      - Voorhees, Walker, Smith and Smith Cocktail Party for Ban. Lane Smith (Nov. 29, 1957), circa 1957 (Box 91, Folder 79)
    - 1958 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - American Society of Landscape Architects, Oliver A. Deakin, 1958-1959 (Box 91, Folder 80)
      - Art Directors Club Meetings and Exhibition, 1958-1959 (Box 91, Folder 81)
      - Art Directors Meeting Luncheons, circa 1958-1959 (Box 91, Folder 82)
      - Hajji Baba Club Dinner, Mr. W. Parsons Todd and Francis Keally, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 83)
      - The Municipal Art Society Luncheons, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 84)
      - National Institute for Architectural Education, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 85)
      - National Society of Art Directors Meetings, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 86)
      - New York Chapter of the A.I.A., Dinners, Luncheons, Meetings - Correspondence, 1958-1959; (2 folders) (Box 91, Folder 87-88)
      - New York Paint Group - Mr. Otto, Luncheon Meetings, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 89)
      - Pratt Architectural Club Meeting and Buffet, 1958-1959 (Box 91, Folder 90)
      - Quiet Birdmen Dinners and Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 91, Folder 91)
      - M.I.T. Class of 1911 Luncheon, Philip L. Caldwell (Jan. 7, 1958), 1957 (Box 91, Folder 92)
      - Edward Fimbel, Inc., D.R. Keegan (Jan. 14, 1958), 1957 (Box 91, Folder 93)
      - Carnegie Institute of Technology Alumni Cocktail Party (Dec. 2, 1958) (Box 91, Folder 94)
      - Art Directors Club Cocktail Party (Dec. 17, 1958) (Box 91, Folder 95)
      - St. Stephen's Alumni Association Cocktail Party (Dec. 19, 1958) (Box 91, Folder 96)
    - 1959 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - American Society of Landscape Architects, Dinners and Meetings, 1959-1966 (Box 91, Folder 97)
      - Art Directors Luncheons and Meetings, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 98)
      - The Municipal Arts Society Luncheons, 1959-1963 (Box 91, Folder 99)
      - National Institute for Architectural Education, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 100)
      - National Sculpture Society, Dinners, Meetings and Exhibitions (1958-1959), 1959-1966 (Box 91, Folder 101)
      - New York Chapter of the American Institute of Architects Luncheons and Meetings, 1959- 1960 (Box 91, Folder 102)
      - New York Paint, Varnish, and Lacquer Association, Inc. Luncheon Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 103)
      - Producers' Council New York Chapter Mardi Gras (Jan. 26-28, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 91, Folder 104)
      - Kentile, Inc. Luncheon (Mar. 10, 1959), 1958 (Box 91, Folder 105)
      - Edison Electric Institute Competition (Mar. 16-17, 1959) (Box 91, Folder 106)
      - American Art Metals Co. Luncheon, Gallery "A" (Apr. 7, 1959) (Box 91, Folder 107)
      - Producers' Council Matico Luncheon (Sept. 22, 1959) (Box 91, Folder 108)
      - Pratt Institute Alumni Dinner (Nov. 18, 1959) (Box 91, Folder 109)
      - Bard-St. Stephen's Alumni Association Cocktail Party (Dec. 18, 1959) (Box 91, Folder 110)
    - A.C.S. Symposium (May 2nd), circa 1960s (Box 91, Folder 111)
    - 1960 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Erich Locker Exhibit and Cocktail Party, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 112)
      - Formica Corporation Dinner, circa 1960-1961 (Box 91, Folder 113)
      - Theta Delta Chi (1960-1961), 1960-1966 (Box 91, Folder 114)
      - Women's Architectural Auxiliary Luncheon, Mrs. Max Urbahn, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 115)
      - Hemophilia Research Inc. Cocktails and Dance, Robert Lee Henry (Jan. 10, 1960), 1959 (Box 91, Folder 116)
      - National Council of the Churches of Christ Meeting and Luncheon (Apr. 1, 1960) (Box 91, Folder 117)
      - Columbia University Alumni Dinner (May 25, 1960) (Box 91, Folder 118)
      - Building Arts Club Dinner (Nov. 22, 1960) (Box 91, Folder 119)
      - Lambda Alpha Fraternity Luncheon (Tue., Dec. 6, 1960), 1960-1961 (Box 91, Folder 120)
      - Abot and Merkt Christmas Luncheon (Dec. 23, 1960) (Box 91, Folder 121)
    - 1961 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Producers' Council Special Luncheons, 1961-1963 (Box 91, Folder 122)
      - Stanford Business School Alumni Luncheon, Mr. Alan C. Root, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 123)
      - Columbia University Alumni Dinner (June 1, 1961) (Box 91, Folder 124)
      - East Island Development, Victor Gruen Associates, Rental of Gallery for Conference (July 1961) (Box 91, Folder 125)
      - Henry Eipel's Cocktail Parties (Nov. 22, 1961 and Nov. 27, 1962), 1961-1965 (Box 91, Folder 126)
      - Caleb Hornbostel Cocktail Party (Dec. 15, 1961) (Box 91, Folder 127)
      - Gruzen and Kelly Christmas Party (Dec. 19, 1961), 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 128)
      - Bard-St. Stephen's Alumni Association Cocktail Party (Dec. 28, 1961), 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 129)
    - 1962 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Hajji Baba Club Dinner Meeting and Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 91, Folder 130)
      - The Johns Hopkins Club of New York, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 131)
      - Crouse-Hinds Company Meetings and Buffet Dinner (Jan. 24, 1962), 1958, 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 132)
      - Rohm and Haas Producers' Council Luncheon (Feb. 27, 1962) (Box 91, Folder 133)
      - Princeton Class of 1935 Luncheon (May 3, 1962) (Box 91, Folder 134)
      - Sargent Company Luncheon (Sept. 11, 1962) (Box 91, Folder 135)
    - 1963 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Quiet Birdmen, Dinners, 1963-1966 (Box 91, Folder 136)
      - Fine Arts Federation Luncheon (Nov. 19, 1963) (Box 91, Folder 137)
      - Westinghouse Corp. Christmas Party, Mr. Sullivan (Dec. 17, 1963), 1961, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 138)
      - Bard-St. Stephen's Alumni Association Cocktail Party (Dec. 20, 1963) (Box 91, Folder 139)
    - 1964 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Women's Architectural Auxiliary, Dinners and Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 91, Folder 140)
      - Columbia University Alumni Dinner (Dec 18?, 1964) (Box 91, Folder 141)
    - 1965 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Columbia University Class of 1909, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 142)
      - New York Chapter of the A.I.A. Cocktail Parties, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 143)
      - Pratt Institute, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 144)
      - Troop "L" Christmas Luncheon, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 145)
      - Women's Architectural Auxiliary Luncheons, 1965-1966 (Box 91, Folder 146)
      - New York State University Construction Fund Dinner (Dec. 2, 1965), 1965-1966 (Box 91, Folder 147)
    - 1966 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 91)
      - Motoquip Inc. Luncheon, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 148)
      - New York Chapter of the A.I.A. Luncheons and Meetings, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 149)
      - Louis Yager Wedding Reception (June 25, 1966) (Box 91, Folder 150)
      - South Atlantic A.I.A. Convention Jury Meeting, W. Crutcher Ross (Aug. 31, 1966) (Box 91, Folder 151)
  - Administrative and Miscellaneous, 1934-1973; 6.3
    Found are announcements and other printed materials, correspondence, receipts, speech transcripts, Current Work Committee files, and other miscellaneous materials related to managing events at the League. Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - Announcements for League Events, Scholarships, Etc., 1971-1973; (3 folders) (Box 92, Folder 1-3)
    - Announcements for League Lectures and Dinners, Current Work Committee, 1939-1963 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Announcements for League Lectures, Current Work Committee, 1946-1961 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Budget Regarding Cost of Forum Luncheons and Dinners (Buffet and Service Type), 1956-1957 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Christmas Fund, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Cocktail Parties, 1946-1968; (8 folders) (Box 92, Folder 8-15)
    - Cost of Dinners, Etc., 1963-1964 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Current Work, Accordion Player, 1940 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Current Work, Mimeographed Copies of Speeches and Speeches Which Have Not Been Mimeographed, 1944-1946; (2 folders) (Box 92, Folder 18-19)
    - Current Work 1935-1936, Glee Club Members, Booklets and Sheets of Xmas Carols, 1934-1937 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Current Work 1938-1939, Reservations re: Luncheons and Dinners-Lists, 1938-1940 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Current Work 1939-1940 (Box 92)
      - Announcements, 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 22)
      - List of Luncheon and Dinner Meetings Held During 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 23)
      - Postal Card Notices, 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 24)
      - (Postal Card Notices) Wednesday Supper Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 25)
      - Reservations for Luncheons and Dinners, 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Current Work 1940-1941, Follow Up (Current Work Leads), Speakers, 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Current Work 1940-1941, Reservations, Luncheon and Dinner Meetings (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Dinner Days Schedule, circa 1953 (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - Dinners, Luncheons and Cocktail Parties, 1950 (Box 92, Folder 30)
    - Edith Halpert, Downtown Gallery, 1941, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 31)
    - Event Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 92, Folder 32)
    - Events, Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 33)
    - Forum, Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 34)
    - Guest Book (Nov. 3, 1954) (Box 92, Folder 35)
    - Itineraries (Developed), 1947-1949 (Box 92, Folder 36)
    - League Events Stats and Printed Materials (Mar. 1968 - May 1970), 1968-1970; (2 folders) (Box 92, Folder 37-38)
    - League Jointly Hosted Parties, 1954-1957 (Box 92, Folder 39)
    - League Printed Material and Correspondence, 1939-1963; (2 folders) (Box 92, Folder 40-41)
    - Letters for Reservations for Exhibitions, Dinners, Luncheons, Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 92, Folder 42)
    - List of Photographs of Buildings To Go in Dining Room, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 43)
    - Luncheon and Dinner Prices for Organizations, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Luncheons, 1954, 1957; (2 folders) (Box 93, Folder 2-3)
    - Mimeographed Notes of League Affairs, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of the Publicity Committee Meeting, 1951 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Potential Prospects for Luncheon, Dinners and Meetings, circa 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Price Increases on Luncheons and Dinners, Letters to Organizations, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Price Quotations, 1960-1963 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Receipts and Expenses, Committee Luncheons, 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Receipts and Expenses, League Dinners, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 93, Folder 10-11)
    - Reservations, 1940-1961; (4 folders) (Box 93, Folder 12-15)
    - Sample Copy, Dinner Event, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Social Events of the League, 1953-1956 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Speeches (Nov. 16, 1944), 1943-1945 (Box 93, Folder 18)